gurumaa.com 2014-11-23

# 

We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We pride ourselves on our commitment to our customers and we feel it is important that we publicize our privacy policy. This section summarizes our privacy policy/practices for gurumaa.com. Personal information is only collected, used and disclosed in accordance with this policy.  
  
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
Personal information about users of this website is obtained if supplied voluntarily, usually through contacting us via e-mail, purchasing of products or registering a user account with us. When you register with us or place an order, we will ask you to set up "My Account," which includes your particulars.  
We collect technical information from your computer's web browser or internet device when you visit gurumaa.com on the internet. This information includes the amount of time spent on the site by a visitor with a unique internet identifier, the pages visited, the operating system, choice of web browser, referring web site and any keywords used to find our site on a search engine website. These server logs contain no personal information and can only be accessed by gurumaa.com. Server log files are used solely to track visits to our website and improve the experience, content and layout of our website. Gurumaa.com makes no attempt to link this site traffic information with the identity of individuals visiting our website.   
  
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We will process your personal data in an ethical manner. It will be used for the following purposes:  
1\. To process your order.  
2\. To administer your membership of the website.  
3\. To administer our website services which may involve sharing information with our services providers.  
4\. To administer our business.  
5\. To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings you are most interested in.  
6\. To allow us to service you better in responding to your customer service requests.  
7\. To notify you of any Products that we think may be of interest to you unless you inform us that you do not wish to receive such information.  
8\. If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you have opted-in not to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails.  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with an advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include gurumaa.com. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, in conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as these partners agree to keep this information confidential. Examples of such companies includes shippers/couriers, credit card companies, banks, and distributors. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.  
  
SECURITY MEASURES  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. When you place orders, you get redirected to payment gateways or the third party.  
For all transactions on www.gurumaa.com, whether it is for purchasing of products or making contributions of registering for events or any other transaction involving movement of funds, we use third party payment processing gateways for all financial transactions. They take all the necessary measures for safe online payment processing.  
We use the following two third party payment processing gateways -  
1. CCAvenue for INR Transactions &   
2. Paypal for USD Transactions  
We do not collect any payment related information like credit card number or bank account details or any other online payment service account details directly on www.gurumaa.com.  
In a nutshell, each time you carry out any transaction on our website, you are redirected to the secure servers of CCAvenue or Paypal for payment processing.  
After the third party has approved your payment, we proceed to the next step of processing your order.  
Note - Paypal is secured & best payment gateway for USD transactions and CCAvenue for INR transactions.    
  
EXTERNAL WEBSITES  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites.  
We encourage visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of these web sites that collect personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by gurumaa.com on this website.  
  
MODIFICATIONS  
To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email schedules you may receive any emails already in process. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.  
  
SPAM  
Your privacy is very important to us. Be assured that, in accordance with this privacy policy, we do not sell or distribute our customer list to third parties. You should be aware, however, that unscrupulous marketers can sometimes ‘harvest’ your e-mail address directly from your computer or another person's address book or even obtain your e-mail address through programs that automatically search web pages and e-mail traffic for e-mail addresses. Gurumaa.com is not responsible for any such event.  
  
ONLINE POLICY ONLY  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
  
TERMS OF SERVICE  
Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.  
  
YOUR CONSENT  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. Gurumaa.com reserves the right to amend this policy at any time and for any reason. An up-to-date policy will always appear on this web site for our visitors. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This ensures that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
  
QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK  
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us your feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue at info@gurumaa.com.
